{
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the galaxy of which our sun is a member?",
        "type": "radio",
        "correct": 2,
        "answers": [
          "Sunflower Galaxy",
          "Cigar Galaxy",
          "Milky Way Galaxy",
          "Comet Galaxy"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "What is special about a chameleon?",
        "type": "radio",
        "correct": 0,
        "answers": [
          "It changes color",
          "It can live without food",
          "It has no eyes",
          "It can live without food and has no eyes",
          "It can breath underwater and fly"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Michael Jordan's nicknames?",
        "caption": "Mark all that apply",
        "type": "checkbox",
        "correct": [0,2,3],
        "answers": [
          "Air Jordan",
          "Black Dog",
          "Black Cat",
          "His airness"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the 'e' of e-mail stand for?",
        "caption": "The answer should be written in lowercase",
        "type": "input",
        "correct": "electronic"
      },
      {
        "question": "What animal is called 'the ship of the desert'?",
        "type": "radio",
        "correct": 2,
        "answers": [
          "Snake",
          "Coyote",
          "Camel",
          "Turtle",
          "Fox"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "What dogs are white with black spots all over them?",
        "type": "radio",
        "correct": 1,
        "answers": [
          "Huskies",
          "Dalmatians",
          "Sheep dog",
          "Alsations"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "What does WWW stand for?",
        "type": "radio",
        "correct": 2,
        "answers": [
          "Widened Web World",
          "Wireless Wide Web",
          "World Wide Web",
          "Window Web World"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "The name of which shampoo brand is made up of two different parts of the body?",
        "type": "radio",
        "correct": 1,
        "answers": [
          "Herbal Essence",
          "Head & Shoulders",
          "Schauma",
          "Pantene"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the 'Big Bang Theory' deal with?",
        "type": "radio",
        "correct": 3,
        "answers": [
          "Medicine",
          "Human Body",
          "Music",
          "Universe"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "What word completes the following idiom. 'Easier Said Than...'?",
        "caption": "The answer should be written in lowercase",
        "type": "input",
        "correct": "done"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the acronym NASA stand for?",
        "caption": "Mark all that apply",
        "type": "radio",
        "correct": 2,
        "answers": [
          "National Army and Soldiers Administration",
          "National Art and Sculpture Administration",
          "National Aeronautics and Space Administration",
          "National Airforce and Special Administration"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Complete the commonly used idiom. 'Better late than ...'",
        "caption": "The answer should be written in lowercase",
        "type": "input",
        "correct": "never"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you want if you send an S.O.S. signal?",
        "type": "radio",
        "correct": 1,
        "answers": [
          "Back-up",
          "Help",
          "Digital Television"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "What does CD stand for?",
        "type": "radio",
        "correct": 2,
        "answers": [
          "Capacity Disk",
          "Copyable Disk",
          "Compact Disc",
          "Circular Disk"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Joseph Barbera and William Hannah created which cat and mouse duo?",
        "type": "radio",
        "correct": 3,
        "answers": [
          "Mickey and Minnie",
          "James and Jerry",
          "Tom and Mickey",
          "Tom and Jerry"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Which is the shortest month of the year?",
        "type": "radio",
        "correct": 3,
        "answers": [
          "September",
          "May",
          "April",
          "February"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "On which continent would you find the fewest people?",
        "type": "radio",
        "correct": 0,
        "answers": [
          "Antarctica",
          "South America",
          "Africa",
          "Europe"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Italian great mind, who made improvements to the telescope, is known as the 'father of modern science'?",
        "type": "radio",
        "correct": 1,
        "answers": [
          "Venturi",
          "Galileo",
          "Rubia",
          "Galvani",
          "Leonardo da Vinci"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the chemical symbol for 'Germanium'?",
        "type": "radio",
        "correct": 3,
        "answers": [
          "Be",
          "Ae",
          "Ce",
          "Ge"
        ]
      }
    ]
  }